“disrespectful language
directed toward Howard Wolowitz,
“including but not limited to:
mockery of engineering,
“his height, his hair,
his wardrobe,
“and his insane belief
that the Ghost Rider movie
was, quote, 'not that bad.'”
(Leonard:)Hang on. Maybe there should be
a “no insult” clause
(Leonard:)about me, too.
(Sheldon:)Do you still like cilantro?
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)You're tying my hands here.
(Howard:)All right, let's sign this.
PENNY: Wait, wait, wait.
(Penny:)What are these changes
on page six?
(Amy:)Sheldon, what did you do?
WOLOWITZ:
I should've known.
“25% of profits
“due to Sheldon Cooper will be
allocated to a scholarship fund
(Bernadette:)for the firstborn child of
Howard and Bernadette Wolowitz”
(Bernadette:)Sheldon, that's so nice.
LEONARD: That beats
(Leonard:)the onesie I was gonna get them
from babyGap.
(Howard:)That's very generous,
Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I've always valued
education over money.
(Sheldon:)And the very fact that you
needed a written guarantee
(Sheldon:)of respect made me realize